Guide to the New York Wine & Grape Foundation records, 1968-2004.
New York Wine & Grape Foundation records}
- Series VIII. Marketing Research
  - Uncork New York!, VHS tape, two cpoies, V-7042, V-7043 (Box 23)
  - NYS DoA Market promotional material, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Steven Auchlich promotional materials, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Bumper stickers, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Vintage keeper, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Display information, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Eggs, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Event and promotion proposals, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Packaging, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Poster, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Promotion Ideas for wineries, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Promotional ideas, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Promotional materials, c. 1980s (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Sign specifications, 1978-1989 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Spectacolor, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Promotional materials, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Marketing, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Promotional materials, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Memos, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - World Trade Centers, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Ketchum Wine Fair, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Liquor Control Board of Ontario materials, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Liquor Control Board of Ontario materials, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Marketing Promotion Program working papers, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Marketing promotion reguations (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Promotional papers, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Waterways and Wineries Grant documents, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Dr. K. Frank Winery information, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - CATS by Katie, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Rochester promotion, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Albany program, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Albany survey, August 1999 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Market survey result Albany/Rochester/Buffalo, November 1999 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Albany, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Winery responses, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - CATS budget information, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Albany CATS program oromotional materials order, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Ad approvals, Albany, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Albany CATS program advertising, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Advertising-on hold for payment processing, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Binghamton/Syracuse CATS, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Buffalo, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Buffalo promotion, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Buffalo CATS program promotion material orders, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Coop. A.D 50/50 Winery, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Rochester CATS program promo material orders, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Rochester, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - CATS, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Advertising, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Uncle Jory's, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Vestal Wine and Liquor, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Vinomania, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Weaver's Wine and Liquor, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - The Wine Sellar, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Western Lights, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Quinnta Jazzwine Kafe, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Robert's Liquors, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - The Roaring Fork, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Rocket Liquors, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Roman's Restaurant, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Ronson's Gold Star Liquors, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Russell's Steak and Seafood, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Seneca Turnpike Liquors, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Seneca Wine and Liquor, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Owego Tradeway Inn, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - P.S Restaurant, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Park Manor Wine and Spirits, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Parkway Wine and Spirits, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Pascale Liquors, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Pepper's Discount W&H, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Peter's Skytop Liquor, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Peter's Liquor, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Plaza Discount Liquors, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Plaza Liquor Store, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Liquor Square, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - The Liquor Store, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Manlius Liquors, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Morey's Restaurant, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Moyers Corners Wines and Spirits, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Northgate Liquors, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Number 5, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Oakdale Wine and Liquor, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Oneida Lake Liquors, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Oswego Plaza Liquors, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Empire Wines, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Giovanni's, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Groton Avenue Liquor Store, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Glendale Spirits, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Hallinan's Liquor Store, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Harbor View Wine and Liquors, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Jamesville Discount Liquors, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Lawler's Liquor Store, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Limestone Liquors, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Liquor City, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - Cortese Restaurant, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - Country Wine and Spirits, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Craftsman House, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - Day Hollow Wine and Liquor, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - Decker's Wine and Spirits, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - Disount Liquor, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 72)
  - Dominick's Restaurant, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 73)
  - Donoli's Restaurant and Banquets, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 74)
  - Eastside Wine and Liquor, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 75)
  - Eckerd Discount Liquor, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 76)
  - Aeillo's Restaurant, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 77)
  - Auburn Discount Liquor and Wine, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 78)
  - Bob's Liquor and Wine, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 79)
  - Bremer's Wine and Liquor, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 80)
  - Cellar Restaurant, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 81)
  - C&D Liquors, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 82)
  - Century Club of Syr, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 83)
  - Champagne Wine and Liquors, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 84)
  - Clay Wine and Spirits, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 85)
  - Coleman's Liquor, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 86)
  - CATS- Saratoga, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 87)
  - CATS- Saratoga April, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 88)
  - Wineries, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 89)
  - Winery Updates, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 90)
  - Winery Updates, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 91)
  - Vineyard Forms (Box 25, Folder 92)
  - August 17 Info Mailing, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 93)
  - Alison Wines, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 94)
  - Amberg, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 95)
  - Anthony Road, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 96)
  - Applewood, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 97)
  - Arbor Hill, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 98)
  - Atwater, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 99)
  - Baldwin Vineyards, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 100)
  - Barrington Cellars, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 101)
  - Batavia Wine Cellars, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 102)
  - Bedell Cellars, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 103)
- Series IX. Newspaper and Press
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1982-1984 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1986-1988 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, March 1985 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, April 1985 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, May 1985 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, June 1985 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, July 1985 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, August, September 1985 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, Oct, Nov, Dec 1985 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, July-August 1983 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, September 1983 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, January-March 1983 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, April-June 1983 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, January-February 1984 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, March-April 1984 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, May-June 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, July 1984 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, August 1984 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, October-December 1984 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper and media clippings: F. Prial, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper and media clippings: Frank T Prial, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper and media clippings: Howard Goldberg, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper and media clippings: Wine on Line, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper and Media clippings: Howard Goldberg, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper and media clippings: Wine Writers, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, 1985-1990 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, 1985-1990 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper and media clippings, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 2001-2004 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Video transcripts, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1981-January 1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, April 1986 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, May 1986 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, June 1986 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, July 1986 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings, August 1986 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings, September 1986 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, October 1986 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings, November 1986 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, December 1986 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, January 1987 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings, February 1987 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper clippings, March 1987 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper clippings, April 1987 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, May 1987 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper clippings, June 1987 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper clippings, July 1987 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper clippings, August 1987 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper clippings, September 1987 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper clippings, October 1987 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper clippings, November 1987 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper clippings, December 1987 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Newspaper clippings, January 1988 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper clippings, February 1988 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper clippings, March 1988 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper clippings, April 1988 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Newspaper clippings, May 1988 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Newspaper clippings, June 1988 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Newspaper clippings, July 1988 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Newspaper clippings, August 1988 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Newspaper clippings, September 1988 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, October 1988 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, November 1988 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, December 1988 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Frank Prial, New York Times, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Howard Goldberg, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Howard Goldberg New York Times, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - New York Times, Frank T Prial, Edward Schumacher, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Business newspaper, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Advertising, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Wine writers, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Wine writers columns, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Wines in the news, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Radio and ad rates, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - All About Wine, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Media relations, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Television, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Ad rates, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Media columns, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - County fairs/farmers market, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Ralph Cipriano/Albany Times Union, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - P. Platanos, 1981-1983 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Ad rates- magazines, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Letters/editor, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Ad rates - magazines, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Cooperative advertising, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Media columns, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Media referrals (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Public TV, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Ad rates/ad agencies, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Advertising, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Wine & Cheese ADA, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Media consultants, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Advertising, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Media contacts, 1980-1986 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Agriculture and Marketing book, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Winery correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Winery correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Winery correspondence, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence from wineries, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence from Glenora, 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Karyl Hammond, 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Cayuga Wine Trail, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Chautauqua County Vacationlands, Inc, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Chautauqua Wine Council, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Events, 1982-1985 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Events, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Hudson River Region Wine Council, 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Hudson River Region Wine Council, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - International Wine Center events, 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - International Wine Center events, New York French American tasting, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - International Wine Center, New York Wine Harvest, September 12 1983 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - International Wine Center events, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - International Wine Center, The Winemakers Choice tasting, April 17. 1986 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - International Wine Center, What's New in New York? tasting, June 2 1986 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - International Wine Center, Riesling tasting, August 13, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Keuka Lake Winery Association, 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Long Island Wineries, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - New York is Wine Country Guide, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Seneca Lake Winery Association, 1982-1986 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Winery calendar, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Tastings, 1980-1986 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Tasting regulations, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Rochester tasting, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - WXXI tastings, 1984-1988 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - New York State Restaurant Association Show tasting, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - New York State Restaurant Association Show tasting, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - New York State Restaurant Association Show tasting, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Syracuse Restaurant promotion, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Vineyard/Winery Investors technical information seminar for New York, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - American Wine Expo Dallas, TX, 1982-1986 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Buckwheat Festival, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Wines From Connecticut, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Dresden Days, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Festivals, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Roundtable for Women in Food Service/A Taste of New York, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - New York Wine Classic, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Entry forms, Hudson River Region and Western New York, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Entry forms, Finger Lakes, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Entry forms, Finger Lakes, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Entry forms, Long Island, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - New York Wine Classic, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Jim Tresize Wine Classic file, 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Entry forms, Canandaigua and North, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Entry forms, Cayuga, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Entry forms, Chautauqua, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Entry forms, Keuka, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Entry forms, Long Island, North Fork, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Entry forms, Long Island, Hamptons, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Entry forms, Seneca, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Entry forms, East, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Entry forms, West, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Gold labels, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - New York Wine Classic judges, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Judges' category comments, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Judges' competition and methodology comments, International Wine Review, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - New York Wine and Food Classic, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Entry forms, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Entry forms, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - New York Wine and Food Classic restaurant recipe forms, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - New York Food and Wine Classic judges, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Judging reports and notes, wine, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Judging reports and notes, wine, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Judging notes food, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Prep Team pull lists, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - New York Wine and Food Classic, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 31)
- Series X. Events
  - Class by the Glass, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Calss by the Glass wineries questionnaires, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Class by the Glass restaurant questionnaires, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Class by the Glass Ithaca (Southern Tier) tasting, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Class by the Glass Ithaca (Southern Tier) tasting, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Class by the Glass Ithaca (Southern Tier) tasting, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Class by the Glass Rochester tasting, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Class by the Glass Rochester winery questionnaire, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Class by the Glass Rochester restaurant questionnaire, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Uncork New York! wine promotion, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Uncork New York! restaurant questionnaires, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Uncork New York winery questionnaires, entry forms, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Northeast restaurants, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Uncork New York restaurant orders, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Uncork New York magazine advertising (New York Alive), 1986 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Uncork New York public television tastings, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Uncork New York winery participation forms, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Uncork New York restaurant questionnaires, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Uncork New York restaurant participation, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Uncork New York Food and Wine promotion, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Uncork New York promotional materials, 1994-2004 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - New York State Fair, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - New York State Fair, 1984-1986 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - New York State Fair, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - New York State Fair, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - New York State Fair, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - New York State Fair, 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Press contacts, vineyards, and individuals lists, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Class by the Glass, May 1987 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Class by the Glass, Albany, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Class by the Glass Albany, Summer 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Class by the Glass, Binghamton, Summer 1987 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Class by the Glass, Brooklyn, New York Metro, May 1987 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Class by the Glass, Buffalo, May 1987 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Class by the Glass, Syracuse, Summer 1987 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Class by the Glass, advertising, newspaper and magazine Clippings, Summer 1987 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Class by the Glass ads, all markets, Summer 1987 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - May restaurant promotion winery agreements, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Wine Tastings, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Class by the Glass, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Class by the Glass, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Class by the Glass Food and Wine Associates proposal, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Class by the Glass, printing, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Class by the Glass winery agreements, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Class by the Glass winery questionnaire, Albany, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Class by the Glass winery questionnaire, New York City, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Class by the Glass winery questionnaire, Rochester, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Class by the Glass winery questionnaire, Southern Tier, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Class by the Glass winery questionnaire, Westchester, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Class by the Glass restaurant questionnaire, Albany, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Class by the Glass restaurant questionnaire, Binghamton, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Class by the Glass restaurant questionnaire, Brooklyn, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Class by the Glass restaurant questionnaire, Buffalo, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Class by the Glass restaurant questionnaire, Rochester, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Class by the Glass restaurant questionnaire, Southern Tier, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Class by the Glass restaurant questionnaire, Syracuse, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Class by the Glass restaurant questionnaire, Westchester, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Class by the Glass restaurant promotion, Westchester, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Class by the Glass tastings, November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Getting Our Slice of the Big Apple, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - International Wine Center events, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - International Wine Center, Sparkling Wines tasting, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - International Wine Center, The Winemakers Choice tasting, March 24, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - International Wine Center, Summer Wines tasting, June 2, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - International Wine Center, New York Riesling: Just How Good is it Getting? tasting, August 12, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - International Wine Center, Chardonnay tasting, October 21, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Public television wine tasting, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Montreal, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Canada free-trade wine, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Producers, 1987-1988 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - "Salute", 1987 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Sherry rebate program, 1987-1996 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Wine Country calendar, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Tourism brochures, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Spring tourism program, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 8)